ZIHUI XU

Jubilee Campus, Nottingham, United Kingdom NG8 1BB | M: 7762363391 | efyzx1@nottingham.ac.uk

SUMMARY

Currently in my second year studying Computer Science in University of Nottingham.

Interested in all aspects of Software development and Big data with experience of using Python, Java. Have a program experience before, especially be familiar with Lightweight development of Java Web could use some tools such as BootStrap,jQuery . Also be familiar with Java Core, for example, could be proficient in using multiple Threads, be familiar with JDBC client and Collection.

Part-time job experiences make me could communicate well with others, could be a good listener and easily get others points.

Communication ability mekes me could always communicate with the team and reflect problems on time.

Technical Experience could make me have foundation to accomplish the technical part of the group project.

EXPERIENCE

09/2018 to 09/2019

part-time job

work in private enterprise

- Used to be an assistant English teacher in a IELTS English school in Wuhan, China Sep 2018-Nov 2018
- Used to be a waiter of MacDonalds in Wuhan, China Oct 2018-Nov2018
- Used to be a saleman of a crab company in Wuhan, China July2019-Sep2019

SKILLS

- Learned C and Java, Arm assembly as Learned framework like part of first year programming modules Bootstrap, Mybatis
- Extremely interested in database
 Learned Interested in database
 Learned Interested in database
 HDFS, HIVE of Huawei GaussDB1.0
- Learned Big data knowledge such as HDES HIVE

EDUCATION

2022

Bachelor of Science: computer science **University of Nottingham** — Nottingham

• Foundation Engineering and Physics Science September 2018–July 2019

PROGRAM EXPERIENCE

Program name: BBS online forum management system

Project description: The system is mainly composed of three modules: home page, user management and post. The home page implements the functions of blurry paging query, post classification, the latest post and the latest message. User management module has functions of login, registration, modify information, view information. The post module includes functions of post, message, view post, modify post and delete post.

Description of duties and responsibilities: completed the user management module individually. Persistence layer was used by Mybatis framework and implemented functions of login, registration, modify information, view information.

JSP page mainly uses JSP tag and struts tag. Both user registration and login use the database form to get the data. And in the page with JavaScript technology for preliminary data verification

Development environment: Database: Oracle